<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-02-28T22:45:12-05:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Progress Time</title><subtitle>This is my Blog where I'll post completed projects and projects in the works. My resume will be visible soon..</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Jumpforce</title><link href="/2019/02/18/JumpForce.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Jumpforce" /><published>2019-02-18T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-02-18T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/2019/02/18/JumpForce</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/02/18/JumpForce.html">&lt;p&gt;Yo whoever was responsible for Jump Froce, ya’ll in big ass trouble. Real talk imma airstrike if I don’t see improvements soon&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Obama</name></author><summary type="html">Yo whoever was responsible for Jump Froce, ya’ll in big ass trouble. Real talk imma airstrike if I don’t see improvements soon</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Wannabe</title><link href="/2019/02/18/Wannabe.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Wannabe" /><published>2019-02-18T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-02-18T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/2019/02/18/Wannabe</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/02/18/Wannabe.html">&lt;p&gt;Ha ha ha ha ha
Yo, I’ll tell you what I want, what I really, really want
So tell me what you want, what you really, really want
I’ll tell you what I want, what I really, really want
So tell me what you want, what you really, really want
I wanna, (ha) I wanna, (ha) I wanna, (ha) I wanna, (ha)
I wanna really, really, really wanna zigazig ah
If you want my future, forget my past
If you wanna get with me, better make it fast
Now don’t go wasting my precious time
Get your act together we could be just fine
I’ll tell you what I want, what I really, really want
So tell me what you want, what you really, really want
I wanna, (ha) I wanna, (ha) I wanna, (ha) I wanna, (ha)
I wanna really, really, really wanna zigazig ah
If you wanna be my lover, you gotta get with my friends
(Gotta get with my friends)
Make it last forever, friendship never ends
If you wanna be my lover, you have got to give
Taking is too easy, but that’s the way it is
Oh, what do you think about that
Now you know how I feel
Say, you can handle my love, are you for real
(Are you for real)
I won’t be hasty, I’ll give you a try
If you really bug me then I’ll say goodbye
Yo I’ll tell you what I want, what I really, really want
So tell me what you want, what you really, really want
I wanna, (ha) I wanna, (ha) I wanna, (ha) I wanna, (ha)
I wanna really, really, really wanna zigazig ah
If you wanna be my lover, you gotta get with my friends
(Gotta get with my friends)
Make it last forever, friendship never ends
If you wanna be my lover, you have got to give
(You’ve got to give)
Taking is too easy, but that’s the way it is
So, here’s a story from A to Z
You wanna get with me, you gotta listen carefully
We got Em in the place who likes it in your face
You got G like MC who likes it on a
Easy V doesn’t come for free, she’s a real lady
And as for me, ha you’ll see
Slam your body down and wind it all around
Slam your body down and wind it all around
If you wanna be my lover, you gotta get with my friends
(Gotta get with my friends)
Make it last forever, friendship never ends
If you wanna be my lover, you have got to give
(You’ve got to give)
Taking is too easy, but that’s the way it is
If you wanna be my lover
You gotta, you gotta, you gotta, you gotta, you gotta
Slam, slam, slam, slam (make it last forever)
Slam your body down and wind it all around
Slam your body down and wind it all around
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha
Slam your body down and wind it all around
Slam your body down and zigazig ah
If you wanna be my lover&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Spice-Girls</name></author><summary type="html">Ha ha ha ha ha Yo, I’ll tell you what I want, what I really, really want So tell me what you want, what you really, really want I’ll tell you what I want, what I really, really want So tell me what you want, what you really, really want I wanna, (ha) I wanna, (ha) I wanna, (ha) I wanna, (ha) I wanna really, really, really wanna zigazig ah If you want my future, forget my past If you wanna get with me, better make it fast Now don’t go wasting my precious time Get your act together we could be just fine I’ll tell you what I want, what I really, really want So tell me what you want, what you really, really want I wanna, (ha) I wanna, (ha) I wanna, (ha) I wanna, (ha) I wanna really, really, really wanna zigazig ah If you wanna be my lover, you gotta get with my friends (Gotta get with my friends) Make it last forever, friendship never ends If you wanna be my lover, you have got to give Taking is too easy, but that’s the way it is Oh, what do you think about that Now you know how I feel Say, you can handle my love, are you for real (Are you for real) I won’t be hasty, I’ll give you a try If you really bug me then I’ll say goodbye Yo I’ll tell you what I want, what I really, really want So tell me what you want, what you really, really want I wanna, (ha) I wanna, (ha) I wanna, (ha) I wanna, (ha) I wanna really, really, really wanna zigazig ah If you wanna be my lover, you gotta get with my friends (Gotta get with my friends) Make it last forever, friendship never ends If you wanna be my lover, you have got to give (You’ve got to give) Taking is too easy, but that’s the way it is So, here’s a story from A to Z You wanna get with me, you gotta listen carefully We got Em in the place who likes it in your face You got G like MC who likes it on a Easy V doesn’t come for free, she’s a real lady And as for me, ha you’ll see Slam your body down and wind it all around Slam your body down and wind it all around If you wanna be my lover, you gotta get with my friends (Gotta get with my friends) Make it last forever, friendship never ends If you wanna be my lover, you have got to give (You’ve got to give) Taking is too easy, but that’s the way it is If you wanna be my lover You gotta, you gotta, you gotta, you gotta, you gotta Slam, slam, slam, slam (make it last forever) Slam your body down and wind it all around Slam your body down and wind it all around Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha Slam your body down and wind it all around Slam your body down and zigazig ah If you wanna be my lover</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome to Jekyll!</title><link href="/jekyll/update/2019/02/17/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to Jekyll!" /><published>2019-02-17T12:27:10-05:00</published><updated>2019-02-17T12:27:10-05:00</updated><id>/jekyll/update/2019/02/17/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="/jekyll/update/2019/02/17/welcome-to-jekyll.html">&lt;p&gt;You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext&lt;/code&gt; and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;'Tom'&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints 'Hi, Tom' to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://jekyllrb.com/docs/home&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">You’ll find this post in your _posts directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run jekyll serve, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Test Test Test</title><link href="/2019/02/17/Test-TeST-TEST.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Test Test Test" /><published>2019-02-17T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-02-17T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/2019/02/17/Test-TeST-TEST</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/02/17/Test-TeST-TEST.html">&lt;p&gt;Testing testing 1 2 3 
Testing testing 4 5 6
Testing testing 98 99 100&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Sett</name></author><summary type="html">Testing testing 1 2 3 Testing testing 4 5 6 Testing testing 98 99 100</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Beginning</title><link href="/2019/02/17/The-Beginning.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Beginning" /><published>2019-02-17T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-02-17T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>/2019/02/17/The-Beginning</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2019/02/17/The-Beginning.html">&lt;p&gt;This is the start. The start of what you may ask.
HA HA HA HA HA HA progress time&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Obama-Chan</name></author><summary type="html">This is the start. The start of what you may ask. HA HA HA HA HA HA progress time</summary></entry></feed>